{"data":[{"question":"____ is needed for the cold winter season.","a":"Much clothing","b":"A lot of clothes","c":"Lots of clothes","d":"Many a cloth","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Clothing [uncountable]: the clothes that people wear \n- \"Is\" implies that the subject is singular- \"a lot of clothes\"' \"lots of clothes; many a cloth\" are not correct","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"I tried every ___to make my best friend give up smoking, but failed.","a":"meaning","b":"mean","c":"ways","d":"means","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Means= method, way","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Three _________ years ago he lived in Shanghai.","a":"score","b":"scores","c":"scores of","d":"score of","answer":"1","explain":"- Three score years= 60 years","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"___ are sold in the new department store.","a":"Men's and women's shoes","b":"Man and woman's shoes","c":"Men's and woman's shoes","d":"Men and women shoes","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Men, women (plural): male and female in general \n- Men's and women's shoes: shoes for both men and women","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"In U.K. ___ are all painted red.","a":"letters boxes","b":"letter boxes","c":"letters box","d":"letter box","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When noun plays role as adjective for other noun, it's always singular- letters is not correct \n- \"Are\" implies that subject is plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"This is the second time in the couple's ___ that we have come to Singapore.","a":"live","b":"life","c":"lifes","d":"lives","answer":"4","explain":"- Couple is two->plural=> life-> lives\n\n- We often say \"couple lives\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"This is an old photo of my mother when she had ___, and now she has ___.","a":"long hairs, grey hairs","b":"long hair, grey hairs","c":"long hairs, grey hair","d":"long hair, grey hair","answer":"2","explain":"- Hair: (uncountable): mentions the whole hair in head\n\n- Hair: (countable): mentions thread of hair\n\nThis case means that in old photo he saw his mother with the long hair, now she still has long hair but some of them are grey","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"There is no greater love than ___ who lays down his life for his country.","a":"a man","b":"that of a man","c":"a man's love","d":"that of a man's","answer":"4","explain":"\n- That of a man's= love of a man, but give more stress on the ownership of the man (man's love)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"When she was combing her hair, I discovered that there were ___ on her shoulders.","a":"a few grey hair","b":"a little grey hair","c":"some grey hair","d":"a few grey hairs","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Hair: (countable): a single piece of hair","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Let's have a ___ break.","a":"ten-minutes","b":"ten minute's","c":"ten minute","d":"ten minutes'","answer":"3","explain":"\n - A ten minute break= a break lengthens 10 minutes","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}